youdagames.com 2015-12-19

# Privacy policy | Youdagames.com

Youdagames respects the privacy of all users of the Youdagames website and ensures personal information provided to us by you will be handled confidentially. Personal details will be processed and secured. Youdagames will hold itself to the demands of the Dutch Data Protection Act (“WBP”) and any local rules and legislation that may apply. The user does need to realise that complete security of data online cannot be guaranteed.

Youdagames will not provide or sell personal data to third parties without prior permission of the user, unless Youdagames is obliged to that end on the grounds of a legal provision or a judicial decision. 

In this Privacy policy you will read about the manner in which Youdagames will manage your personal data. The use of the Youdagames website entails acceptance of this Privacy policy and any modifications thereof. This page will give notice of these modifications.

### Personal data

Youdagames may acquire your personal data in the event of you subscribing for a service or buying a product for the first time. Youdagames may acquire the following personal data: name, surname, address, e-mail address, phone number, bank and payment details. 

Furthermore, anonymous data may be acquired; these are coupled to your IP-address. When you visit the Youdagames website, it is necessary to gather certain information in order for the connection to run smoothly. The information coupled to the IP-address, such as searches and previously visited websites, cannot be traced back to the user. Also, Youdagames may use the IP-address for composing user statistics.

### Cookies

During a visit to the website, mainly through the use of a cookie Youdagames can gather data of a non-personal nature. A cookie is a small text file that a server can place on the hard drive of the computer of the user. A cookie contains information about the visit of the user to the Youdagames website. Cookies can be used to gather certain information during the visit of the user to the Youdagames website. These data help to better tune Youda and the Youdagames website and the services to the wishes and preferences of the user of the website. You can set up your Internet browser in such a way that you will receive a notification when a new cookie is saved onto your computer. You will receive the option of accepting or refusing this. For more specific information, please refer to the help function of your Internet browser. Please take into account that parts of the Youdagames website will not function properly if you refuse to enable cookies.

### The use of your personal data

Youdagames uses your username, e-mail address and password to identify you as a user of the Youdagames website. Youdagames has permission to show your user name or use it for a ranking. 

Any other personal data you provided during your registration with the Youdagames website can be used for statistical goals and/or sending newsletters to your e-mail address.

### E-mail / opt-in / opt-out

When you register for an account with Youdagames, you have the option to indicate whether you would like to receive the Youdagames newsletter (“opt-in”). You have the possibility to cancel your subscription to the newsletter at all times by selecting the link “cancel subscription”. This link has been incorporated at the end of every Youdagames newsletter. 

### Right concerning your personal data

As a user you have the right at all times to request of Youdagames which personal data regarding yourself have been saved in the database. When you are of the opinion those personal data are not (or no longer) correct or complete, you can request of Youdagames to complete, correct or delete your personal data. Furthermore, you have the right at all times to object to the use of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. To this end you can address your request for inspection, correction and/or deletion to.

Youda Games Holding BV   
Postbus 22223   
1100 CE Amsterdam   
The Netherlands
